RADWAN AHMED

Front End Engineer | UI Developer

- +8801873-843384
- github.com/radwan503
- madwananik.netlify.app/
- □ radwananik.ra@gmail.com
- linkedin.com/in/radwananik/

A qualified and enthusiastic person, with 3+ years' experience. Excellent analytical and organizational skills. I am a self-motivated individual that can give 100% in everything I do. Designated as Front End Engineer with 3+ years of solid experience in Software Industry. Develop product as business first minded.

SKILL

WEB/TECH

- HTML5,
- CSS3,
- JavaScript

FRAMEWORK

- React JS | Next JS
- Ionic | Jquery
- Bootstrap | SCSS
- TailwindCss | Material UI | Antd

TOOL

• Git | Jasper Report | Redmine

CMS

WordPress

Design

Figma | Adobe XD

EDUCATION

 Daffodil International University Bachelor of Science, Computer Science & Engineering 2015 – 2019 | Dhaka | Bangladesh

CERTIFICATION

- CERTIFICATE ON JAVASCRIPT PROGRAMMING | Stydysection
- JQUERY UI WIDGET | Udemy
- RAPID USABILITY RESEARCH FOR UX | Udemy

WORK EXPERIENCE

Tiger IT Bangladesh Ltd Front-End Engineer | UI Developer May 2019-present

- Building websites and apps that are device responsive and usable
- Consuming and integrating restful APIs in a JS application.
- Optimize applications for maximum speed.

Freelancer

UI Developer

May 2019-present

- Hand coding HTML5 and CSS3 also Test code across platforms and browsers.
- Responsive Design on to develop user interface on web and mobile.
- Slicing and enhancing of PSD files, creating pixel -perfect renderings.

PROJECT

HRM MANAGEMENT (WEB)

- Design and develop this system for gathering all the employee information in one tool.
- Employee day to day, monthly and yearly attendance, leave, working hour information etc.
- Searching system for getting details and update.
- Report generating system using Jasper report tool etc.

TECH STACK: HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, JAVA, JSP

ACTION TRACKER (WEB & APP)

- Issue and Problem wise project create and assign team member.
- Chatting with manager, owner and employee based on authentication.
- Collaboration With team based on project issue.

TECH STACK: REACT, IONIC, SCSS

FORUM (Demo)

 Developing forum Template using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, and Jquery. Design with your posting question and separate different category like recent, most response, and recent answer.